<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Kitty corner of the internet</title>
    <link>https://www.khatnaps.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Kitty corner of the internet</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 14:20:31 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.khatnaps.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn baby</title>
      <link>https://www.khatnaps.net/posts/brooklyn-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 14:20:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.khatnaps.net/posts/brooklyn-baby/</guid>
      <description>And so the best of 2024 lingers on into the new year. &lt;em&gt;Anora (2024)&lt;/em&gt; leaves me with an intangible feeling, one that strikes an emotional core like no other feminist-adjacent media has done in recent memory. i feel something fundamentally true to the feminine condition in Mikey Madisons performance as Anora. and i cant unfeel it, despite the months that go by since seeing this movie&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The substance</title>
      <link>https://www.khatnaps.net/posts/the-substance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:20:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.khatnaps.net/posts/the-substance/</guid>
      <description>Trying not to think about being in a body- an affair i’ve been at for awhile. October seems to agree, with its ghouls and guts and flesh, that being in a being in a body is horrifying. And then i watched &lt;em&gt;The Substance (2024)&lt;/em&gt;.  there’s plenty needles, repeated injection, surgical stitchery, mukbang-style slobbering over prawns&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark academia</title>
      <link>https://www.khatnaps.net/posts/dark-academia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:20:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.khatnaps.net/posts/dark-academia/</guid>
      <description>August did send its warning to the northeast- that week-long false break from humidity and stillness. along with, the wind blew away my sense of stopped time. at least, the weight of sunset falls square on the shoulders now. as the night bites back, rightly blue to righteous black, the summer is weathering down. and im so much more alert for it. i fear losing light never hurt so good&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweet like sugar water</title>
      <link>https://www.khatnaps.net/posts/sugar-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 14:20:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.khatnaps.net/posts/sugar-water/</guid>
      <description>I am sitting in a forest inside a botanic garden, where everything is in bloom. the last of summer lies ahead. today, the greenhouses were open to the public and all the flower beds seem to glisten, bathing in light and sugar water.  and then it occurs to me that late August captures the precise seasonality of the album (Maude Latours debut Sugar Water)&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.khatnaps.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.khatnaps.net/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a cat on the internet :). you can reach me at kha.t.huynh@gmail.com.&#xA;I am a cat that will never learn to drive because i was born and raised in Boston. i studied urban ecology, public transit, and clam chowdery at Carleton College&amp;rsquo;s American Studies department. i am seeking representation for my debut novella which explores the current critiques of suburbia and gentrification through ecological motifs. the sorts of invasive species like the moth effect (formerly known as butterfly effect), the tree of heaven, and cats with souls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.khatnaps.net/book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.khatnaps.net/book/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been working on a novella (magical realism, science and literary fiction) with aims to publish in Summer/Fall 2025.&#xA;&amp;hellip;After years of radio silence, two friends reconnect in their hometown of Boston. In just 24 hours, they unearth spirits from old stomping grounds, setting forth a timeline of biblical proportion. One friend is human. The other will forever and always be a moth.&#xA;Their friendship is fraught to say the least.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
